<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE locale SYSTEM "../../../../../lib/pkp/dtd/locale.dtd">

<!--
  * plugins/generic/oas/locale/en_US/locale.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2012 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Localization strings.
  -->
 
<locale name="en_US" full_name="U.S. English">
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.displayName">Open Access Statistics (OA-S)</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.description"><![CDATA[The OA-S plugin transforms OJS into a data provider for the <a href="http://www.dini.de/projekte/oa-statistik" target="_new">Open Access Statistics (OA-S) project</a>.]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.report.displayName">OA-S Reporting</message>
	<message key="plugins.reports.oas.report.description">This plugin implements reports based on OA-S metrics.</message>
	
	<message key="plugins.reports.oas.metricType.counter">OA-S/COUNTER</message>
	<message key="plugins.reports.oas.metricType.counter.full">Open Access Statistics: COUNTER</message>
	
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optin">Opt In</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout">Opt Out</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout.description">Open Access Statistics (OA-S) Privacy Information</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout.displayName">OA-S Privacy Information</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout.done">You successfully opted out from usage statistics collection. While you see this message no statistics will be collected from your usage of this site. Click the below button to revert your decision.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout.title">Privacy Information</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout.link">Read more...</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout.shortDesc"><![CDATA[We log anonymous usage statistics. Please read the <a href="{$privacyInfo}">privacy information</a> for details.]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout.cookie">
		If you click the opt-out button below then your browser will receive an "opt-out cookie" and no statistics information will be collected at all as long as
		this cookie is present in your browser. The opt-out information will be stored for one year and will be renewed for another year whenever you access OJS. The
		cookie contains no information that may be used to identify you. Please note that if you are using a different browser or if you delete cookies from your
		browser then you'll have to opt-out again as we'll not keep any personal information about you on our side to protect your privacy.
	</message>
	
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.updateStatisticsError">Error while updating statistics</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.updateStatisticsSuccess">Successfully updated statistics</message>

	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings">Settings</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.admin">OA-S Plugin Administration</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.adminDescription">
		You have got two options to download aggregate statistics from the OA-S server: You can either set up a cronjob (see README in the plugin directory) or
		update statistics manually by clicking the button below.
	</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.adminUpdate">Update Statistics</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oaiPassword">OAI-PMH Password</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oaiPasswordInstructions">Please provide a password to prevent unauthorized access to your raw statistics data.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oaiPasswordRequired">Please enter a password that protects your statistics data from unauthorized access.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasDataProviderDescription">
		Your usage statistics will be transferred to OA-S via a so-called "OAI-PMH" interface. You have to protect that interface
		from unauthorized access by setting a self-chosen password. This is necessary to guarantee your users' privacy. When registering
		to participate in the OA-S system you'll have to provide this password so that the OA-S server can retrieve your statistics data.
		The corresponding username 'ojs-oas' is fixed in OJS. Please use the username 'ojs-oas' together with your password to register for OA-S.
	</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasDataProviderSettings">Data Provider settings (Statistics export)</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasServerPassword">Password</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasServerPasswordInstructions">Please enter the OA-S statistics server password.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasServerPasswordRequired">Please enter a valid password to authenticate to the OA-S statistics server.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasServerUrl">Statistics Server URL</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasServerUrlInstructions">Please enter the OA-S statistics server URL you received from the OA-S project (example: https://oase.gbv.de/ojs-test/).</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasServerUrlRequired">Please enter a valid OA-S statistics server URL (example: https://oase.gbv.de/ojs-test/).</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasServerUsername">Username</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasServerUsernameInstructions">Please enter the OA-S statistics server username you received from the OA-S project.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasServerUsernameRequired">Please enter a valid username to authenticate to the OA-S statistics server (colons are disallowed).</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasServiceProviderDescription">
		Consolidated and cleansed usage statistics will be automatically be downloaded from the OA-S statistics server. Once you registered to
		participate in the OA-S project, you'll receive a username and password to access that statistics server. Please enter these
		credentials here.
	</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasServiceProviderSettings">Service Provider settings (Statistics import)</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasSettings">OA-S Plugin: Settings</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.privacyDescription">
		Transferring statistics data to OA-S may have direct or indirect implications for your users' privacy. Please check whether
		you are liable to provide a privacy message to your end users. Notwithstanding other legislation this is usually the case
		if you have to comply with German privacy legislation. This message will appear when users click on the "privacy information"
		link that automatically comes with this plug-in.
	</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.privacyMessage">Privacy Message</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.privacyMessageInstructions">Please enter a privacy message.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.privacySettings">Privacy settings</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiDescription"><![CDATA[
		The OA-S plugin requires access to a SALT server to pseudonimize IP addresses. After registering your OJS installation with the OA-S project you'll
		receive a username and password from University Library Saarbrücken (SULB). Please enter these login credentials here so that you are able to use the
		plug-in.
	]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiPassword">Password</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiPasswordInstructions">Please enter the corresponding SALT server password.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiPasswordRequired">Please enter a valid password to authenticate to the SALT server.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiUsername">Username</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiUsernameInstructions">Please enter the OA-S SALT server username you received from University Saarbrücken.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiUsernameRequired">Please enter a valid username to authenticate to the SALT server (colons are disallowed).</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiSettings">SALT server settings</message>
</locale>
